<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Money poor, mission rich]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Money poor, mission rich]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/missionaire/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 04:40:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/missionaire/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>I miss my dog. More than I thought I would but not to any detriment, I just remember holding Winston in my hand with room to spare 2 years ago this week. I miss standing in the open door of a Pac 750XL, 15,000ft up on a beautiful Nagambie day and the friends I made on columns of air as I embraced gravity and its reliable reaction to my letting go of the plane. I miss my Yamaha R1 and the track days and winding country roads that facilitated my escape and evasion of the myriad of problems I’d played at the minimum, a lead role in creating. I miss my V8 ute and the downhill mountain bikes, trail bikes and road bikes that had at one time been in the back while I made my way out to beautiful parts of Australia with a best mate, to put the pedals underfoot and just talk while we covered thousands of kilometres together. I miss running the trails of surrounding Melbourne, the conversations that I could sustain early on with a man I’m lucky to call a friend and listening to his observations when I was struggling to breathe – the best part being at the end when I saw how happy he was for having been out there.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/missionaire/coming-soon/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8a6c7036-b3cb-4674-acc9-97eb8deff08d</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 04:38:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>